---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://critterism-be.herokuapp.com/api/v1/trivia
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      User-Agent:
      - Faraday v2.6.0
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Server:
      - Cowboy
      Date:
      - Tue, 08 Nov 2022 23:13:53 GMT
      Connection:
      - keep-alive
      Content-Type:
      - application/json; charset=utf-8
      Etag:
      - W/"b36556e529aa6abcfad251e2e2cc3721"
      Cache-Control:
      - max-age=0, private, must-revalidate
      X-Request-Id:
      - 3b7787d8-b073-491c-a25d-747f9581e1ae
      X-Runtime:
      - '0.028173'
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Via:
      - 1.1 vegur
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"data":[{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        is the scientific name for modern day humans?","correct_answer":"Homo Sapiens","incorrect_answers":["Homo
        Ergaster","Homo Erectus","Homo Neanderthalensis"],"answers":["Homo Ergaster","Homo
        Erectus","Homo Neanderthalensis","Homo Sapiens"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"How
        many legs do butterflies have?","correct_answer":"6","incorrect_answers":["2","4","0"],"answers":["2","4","0","6"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What
        scientific family does the Aardwolf belong to?","correct_answer":"Hyaenidae","incorrect_answers":["Canidae","Felidae","Eupleridae"],"answers":["Canidae","Felidae","Eupleridae","Hyaenidae"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which
        class of animals are newts members of?","correct_answer":"Amphibian","incorrect_answers":["Fish","Reptiles","Mammals"],"answers":["Fish","Reptiles","Mammals","Amphibian"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        is the scientific name of the Common Chimpanzee?","correct_answer":"Pan troglodytes","incorrect_answers":["Gorilla
        gorilla","Pan paniscus","Panthera leo"],"answers":["Gorilla gorilla","Pan
        paniscus","Panthera leo","Pan troglodytes"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"By
        definition, where does an abyssopelagic animal live?","correct_answer":"At
        the bottom of the ocean","incorrect_answers":["In the desert","On top of a
        mountain","Inside a tree"],"answers":["In the desert","On top of a mountain","Inside
        a tree","At the bottom of the ocean"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        is the common term for bovine spongiform encephalopathy (BSE)?","correct_answer":"Mad
        Cow disease","incorrect_answers":["Weil\u0026#039;s disease","Milk fever","Foot-and-mouth
        disease"],"answers":["Weil\u0026#039;s disease","Milk fever","Foot-and-mouth
        disease","Mad Cow disease"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"How
        many teeth does an adult rabbit have?","correct_answer":"28","incorrect_answers":["30","26","24"],"answers":["30","26","24","28"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        is the collective noun for bears?","correct_answer":"Sloth","incorrect_answers":["Drove","Tribe","Husk"],"answers":["Drove","Tribe","Husk","Sloth"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        is the collective noun for rats?","correct_answer":"Mischief","incorrect_answers":["Pack","Race","Drift"],"answers":["Pack","Race","Drift","Mischief"]}}]}'
  recorded_at: Tue, 08 Nov 2022 23:13:53 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.1.0
